(Bernadette:)I was thinking of going
to the lecture
(Bernadette:)on posterior cingulate
cortex lesions
(Bernadette:)in the formation
of autobiographical memory.
(Amy:)Oh, brain lesions are fascinating.
(Amy:)Unless they're yours,
than they're a drag.
(Bernadette:)To the advancement of science.
(Amy:)And to the sick and dying
who make it possible.
(Bernadette:)This is fun. We never really get
to talk shop with Penny around.
(Bernadette:)We usually just end up
talking about boys.
(Amy:)Which is fine,
but it's nice to mix it up
(Amy:)with a little
intellectual conversation.
(Waiter:)From the two gentlemen at the bar.
Oh, my gosh, boys bought us drinks!
Boys bought us drinks!
(Amy:)Thank you, thank you,
thank you so much.
(Bernadette:)-Be cool.
-You be cool!
(Amy:)Guys are hitting on us,
and not just to get to Penny.
You're right. Thank you!
-Oh! Bad move.
-Really? Why?